Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering Records UA240
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering Records
1890 -- 2018
1960 -- 2012
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering
UA240
19.1 Linear Feet
The Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering Records document the administration and activities of the department.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred by the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering, 2018.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in eight series: Student files; Office files; Course files; Faculty files; Eta Kappa Nu files; Photographs; 2017 accessions; and 2018 accessions. Arrangement within series varies; original order was maintained where discernible.
Biographical / Historical
The Department of Electrical Engineering has its origins in a three-year course of study in "Electrical Science" instituted in 1883. Though the program was initially held "as demand warranted it", it became popular enough to formally establish the Department of Electrical Engineering in 1890. After expanding its curriculum to include computer science classes, the department was renamed the Department of Electrical Engineering and Computer Science in 1994. In 2003, the department became the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering, and the Department of Computer Science split off into its own department. The program was originally a three-year program focused in Electrical Science, with a concentration in commercial applications. The resulting degree was a Bachelor of Mechanic Arts, with the designation of "Electrical" to appear on the diploma. However, for the 1892-1893 academic year, the engineering curriculum was increased to a four-year plan of study, with candidates for degrees to be awarded a Bachelor of Electrical Engineering. This increase resulted in a housing crisis that touched on each engineering department; though the Department of Electrical Engineering was originally housed in Ballou Hall, it utilized the newly added Bromfield Pearson School, Robinson Hall, and Howe Laboratory for laboratory and classroom space in subsequent years. The Department of Electrical Engineering had a close connection with the American Radio and Research Corporation (AMRAD) while the company was active on campus. AMRAD had built two buildings in close proximity to Tufts; a small laboratory in 1915 on the north side of campus, and a manufacturing plant in 1920 across the Boston and Maine railroad tracks. The Department of Electrical Engineering used the laboratory facilities for several years to provide training in radio communications. After AMRAD declared bankruptcy in 1925 and sold its buildings to Tufts, the Electrical Engineering Department used the laboratory as its headquarters. In 1931, during the construction of Cousens Gymnasium, the manufacturing plant was renovated to become a wing of the gym. After construction was complete, the Department of Electrical Engineering moved to this wing. This wing was dedicated as Hooper Laboratory in 1940 and was later renovated and renamed Halligan Hall in 1983. As of 2017, it continues to house the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering as well as the Department of Computer Science. From 1890 until his death in 1918, William Hooper served as the department's only full professor. Additional influential figures who served the department were Edwin B. Rollins, full professor and chair of the department from 1928 to 1943, and Melville S. Munro, who acted as a professor of the department from 1913 to 1941. Noticeable increases in enrollment have occurred twice in the department's history. From the early 20th century through the First World War, all departments within the Engineering School faced a rapid increase in interest, resulting in overenrollment. Though 1907 changes in admissions standards somewhat relieved the problem, the school remained over-enrolled until the 1920s, when the curriculum was revised and enrollment waned. During the 1970s and into the late 1980s, enrollment in the Department of Electrical Engineering surged, with the number of students graduating from the department peaking close to 100 in 1987. This increase in enrollment was attributed to increased interest in computers. After 1987, the number of degrees granted by the department steadily decreased until the early 1990's, when the number of degrees granted each year remained steady. The introduction of a Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering in 1994 has not changed the enrollment of the department in either direction; the combined number of degrees in Electrical Engineering and Computer Engineering remained consistent with the number of degrees previously granted in Electrical Engineering alone.
Scope and Contents
The Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering records document the administration and activities of the department, including administrative files, faculty files, student academic records, and course documentation. Also included are department-related news clippings and newsletters as well as an extensive collection of photographs.
Tufts University. Department of Electrical Engineering and Computer Science.; Student life
- Student files, 1993 -- 2012; UA240.001; 2.4 Linear Feet
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically within each accession.
  Conditions Governing Access
  75 years from the date of creation.
  - Agarwal, Vinay, 2006 -- 2008; UA240.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Master of Science in Electrical Engineering
  - Akapo, Olusola, 2006 -- 2008; UA240.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Almoayed, Nawaf, 2001 -- 2008; UA240.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    Doctor of Philosophy in Electrical Engineering
  - Arous, Anthony E, 2004 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Ashkouri, Samer, 2004 -- 2006; UA240.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Austin, Eric, 2004 -- 2008; UA240.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Bahadoor, Adil, 2003 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Blachandran, Sumugam, 1999 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    Master of Science in Electrical Engineering, withdrew from PhD program
  - Barnett, Bryan, 2007 -- 2008; UA240.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    Master of Science
  - Baron, Matthew, 2004 -- 2006; UA240.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    Withdrawn
  - Basu, Prabahan, 2001 -- 2007; UA240.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    Master of Science in Electrical Engineering (2003,) PhD in Electrical Engineering (2007)
  - Bishop, Robert, 2003 -- 2007; UA240.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Bnari, Jamal, 2003 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Botha, David, 2003 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Bottari, John A, 1999 -- 2007; UA240.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
    Withdrawn from PhD
  - Bowen, Christopher, 2005; UA240.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Bradley, Clifton B, 2004 -- 2006; UA240.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Brassard, Joseph, 2003 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Brittain, Candice, 2003 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Brock, Lindsey M, 2005 -- 2006; UA240.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Brown, Nathan, 2004 -- 2006; UA240.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Bruch, Kurt O, 2004 -- 2006; UA240.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Bruno, Stephen C, 2003 -- 2010; UA240.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Bruso, Albert, 2004 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Bu, Lixiang, 2006 -- 2008; UA240.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Burdin, Jared, 2003 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Caccese, James W, 2003 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Chang, Kimberlee, 2004 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Chen, Shu, 2003 -- 2008; UA240.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - Chow, Jon W, 2004 -- 2006; UA240.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Crane, David, 2006; UA240.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Creamer, Michael, 2003 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Crane, Jeffrey, 2005 -- 2006; UA240.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - Daley, Leah, 2007 -- 2008; UA240.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - Danahy, Ethan (1 of 2), 2002 -- 2007; UA240.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - Danahy, Ethan (2 of 2), 2000 -- 2002; UA240.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
    Master of Science in Computer Science
  - Daphtary, Milan, 2006; UA240.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
    Last enrolled in 2006
  - Doran, Kyle, 2006 -- 2007; UA240.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - Dorsch, Matthew, 2004 -- 2008; UA240.001.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - Evans, Eric, 2004 -- 2006; UA240.001.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - Ferrara, Joseph, 2004 -- 2006; UA240.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - Geisler, Carl J, 2001 -- 2008; UA240.001.001.00042 (Box 1)
  - Gentile, Andrew, 2005 -- 2010; UA240.001.001.00043 (Box 1)
  - Egan, Nathan, 2002 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00044 (Box 1)
  - Gosain, Abhimanyu, 2006 -- 2008; UA240.001.001.00045 (Box 1)
  - Govindarajan,Barghavi, 2007 -- 2008; UA240.001.001.00046 (Box 1)
  - Grout, Laura, 2004 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00047 (Box 1)
  - Hachadorian, Joseph, 2004 -- 2007; UA240.001.001.00048 (Box 1)
  - Hallacoglu, Bertan, 2007 -- 2008; UA240.001.001.00049 (Box 1)
  - Haque, Shayan, 2002 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00050 (Box 1)
  - Harris, Brian, 2003 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00051 (Box 1)
  - Harris, Scott, 2005 -- 2007; UA240.001.001.00052 (Box 1)
  - Howarth, Dean, 2006 -- 2007; UA240.001.001.00053 (Box 1)
  - Ingersoll, Brett, 2000 -- 2006; UA240.001.001.00054 (Box 1)
  - Iwamoto, Yasumichi, 2003 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00055 (Box 1)
  - Johnson, Richard, 2001 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00056 (Box 1)
  - Kabir, Raonaak, 2006 -- 2008; UA240.001.001.00057 (Box 1)
  - Karim, Lutfi, 2008; UA240.001.001.00058 (Box 1)
  - Kessler, Brian, 2005 -- 2007; UA240.001.001.00059 (Box 1)
  - Khan, Usman, 2001 -- 2008; UA240.001.001.00060 (Box 1)
  - Kim, Hyon, 2004 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00061 (Box 1)
  - Kim, Wonjae, 2005 -- 2006; UA240.001.001.00062 (Box 1)
  - Kotwal, James, 2005 -- 2008; UA240.001.001.00063 (Box 1)
  - Komoni, Krenar, 2006 -- 2008; UA240.001.001.00064 (Box 1)
  - Kratzenberg, Eric W, 1997 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00065 (Box 1)
  - Law, Matthew, 2002 -- 2007; UA240.001.001.00066 (Box 1)
  - Lalooses, Francine, 2005 -- 2007; UA240.001.001.00067 (Box 1)
    Transferred to Computer Science
  - Landman, Dan, 2002 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00068 (Box 1)
  - Leschuk, Steven, 2003 -- 2005; UA240.001.001.00069 (Box 1)
  - Lian, Elana, 2005 -- 2007; UA240.001.001.00070 (Box 1)
  - Lin, Mi, 2004 -- 2006; UA240.001.001.00071 (Box 1)
  - Liporto, Scott, 2005 -- 2007; UA240.001.001.00072 (Box 1)
  - Luo, Zhenying, 2005 -- 2007; UA240.001.001.00073 (Box 1)
  - Magpayo, Matthew, 2005 -- 2006; UA240.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - MacRostie, Ehry, 2006 -- 2009; UA240.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Matranga, Michael, 2003 -- 2007; UA240.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Mayer, Linda M, 2005 -- 2007; UA240.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - McCloskey, Gregory, 2003 -- 2006; UA240.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Mercier, Shane, 2005 -- 2007; UA240.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Mueller, Wayne, 2001 -- 2008; UA240.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - Morgan, Jaina, 2006 -- 2008; UA240.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Natarajan, Premkumar, 1993 -- 1996; UA240.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Nercessian, Armen, 2005 -- 2007; UA240.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Peloquin, Stuart, 2003 -- 2005; UA240.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Perez Sanchez, Ariel, 2004 -- 2006; UA240.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Perova, Natalia, 2003 -- 2005; UA240.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Pringle, James, 2006 -- 2008; UA240.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Pulaha, Eduart, 2003 -- 2005; UA240.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Qazi, Sadaf, 2006 -- 2008; UA240.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Ranger, Elliot R, 2006 -- 2007; UA240.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Ries, David, 2004 -- 2006; UA240.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Robinton, Mark E, 2005 -- 2007; UA240.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Rimkunas, Zach, 2003 -- 2005; UA240.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Rodrigues, Carl, 2006 -- 2008; UA240.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - Rotker, Nicholas, 2006 -- 2008; UA240.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Rowell, Adam S, 2005; UA240.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - Schelly, Jennifer, 2005 -- 2006; UA240.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Schundler, Elizabeth, 2006 -- 2008; UA240.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Sergi, John-David, 2004 -- 2005; UA240.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Shukla, Neeraj, 2008; UA240.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Silva, Eric, 2004 -- 2007; UA240.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Siu, Wing, 2004 -- 2007; UA240.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Souri, Ramy, 2002 -- 2007; UA240.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Subramanian, Lakshmi, 2001 -- 2006; UA240.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - Swahn, Brian, 2001 -- 2006; UA240.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
    Doctor of Philosophy
  - Suwanvisan, Nattakarn, 2003 -- 2005; UA240.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - Truhlar, Gregory, 2006 -- 2007; UA240.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - Varanasi, Krishna Tej, 2005 -- 2008; UA240.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - Vasquez, Scott, 2005 -- 2008; UA240.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
  - Vereda, Fernando, 1997 -- 2003; UA240.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - Wilson, James E, 2007; UA240.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
  - Vidyarthi, Arvind, 2002 -- 2005; UA240.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - Virgil, Cedric, 2005 -- 2007; UA240.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - Wang, Jiahui, 2003 -- 2005; UA240.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
  - Wang, Xiaofeng, 2004 -- 2005; UA240.001.002.00042 (Box 2)
  - Wangai, Robert, 2004 -- 2006; UA240.001.002.00043 (Box 2)
  - Waterman, Jason, 2005 -- 2007; UA240.001.002.00044 (Box 2)
  - Weintraub, Marc, 2004 -- 2006; UA240.001.002.00045 (Box 2)
  - Wharton, Eric, 2006 -- 2008; UA240.001.002.00046 (Box 2)
  - Wilkinson, John, 2005 -- 2006; UA240.001.002.00047 (Box 2)
  - Wilson, Adam, 2004 -- 2005; UA240.001.002.00048 (Box 2)
  - Wolf, Andrew, 2012; UA240.001.002.00049 (Box 2)
    Bachelor of Science/Master of Science
  - Wu, Chengyuan, 2003 -- 2008; UA240.001.002.00050 (Box 2)
  - Xu, Siming, 2007; UA240.001.002.00051 (Box 2)
  - Yang, Jinyoung, 2006 -- 2010; UA240.001.002.00052 (Box 2)
  - Yildiz, Oyku, 2002 -- 2007; UA240.001.002.00053 (Box 2)
  - Yu, Vincent K, 2004 -- 2008; UA240.001.002.00054 (Box 2)
  - Zhang, Yiling, 2006 -- 2008; UA240.001.002.00055 (Box 2)
  - Robinton, Mark Edward, 2005; UA240.001.002.00056 (Box 2)
    Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering
  - Schaevitz, Rebecca Kayla, 2005; UA240.001.002.00057 (Box 2)
  - Schlossberg, Ellen, 2005; UA240.001.002.00058 (Box 2)
  - Silver, Blair Alexander, 2005; UA240.001.002.00059 (Box 2)
  - Roy, Christopher Ryan, 2005; UA240.001.002.00060 (Box 2)
  - Vigil, Cedric Alexander, 2005; UA240.001.002.00061 (Box 2)
- Office files, 1985 -- 2010; UA240.002; 1.2 Linear Feet
  Office files include budgets, degree program descriptions and records, faculty meeting minutes, evaluations and reports related to the ABET accreditation process for the School of Engineering, department-related news clippings, and the department newsletter.
  This series is arranged as received from the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering.
  20 years from date of creation.
  - Office files, 1985 -- 2010; UA240.002.003 (Box 3)
    Office files include budgets; degree program descriptions and records; faculty meeting minutes; evaluations and reports related to the ABET accreditation process for the School of Engineering, 2003; department-related news clippings, 1985-2010; and the department newsletter, 2007-2010.
- Course files, 2004 -- 2010; UA240.003; 2.4 Linear Feet
  Electrical and Computer Engineering course materials include syllabi, handbooks, workbooks, lab assignments, and exams. Also included are lists of courses offered and assigned books.
  This series is arranged numerically by course number.
  - Course files (1 of 2), 2004 -- 2009; UA240.003.004 (Box 4)
    Electrical and Computer Engineering course materials include syllabi, handbooks, workbooks, lab assignments, and exams for courses EN-1 through EE-50, 2004-2009.
  - Course files (2 of 2), 2004 -- 2010; UA240.003.005 (Box 5)
    Electrical and Computer Engineering course materials include syllabi, handbooks, workbooks, lab assignments, and exams for courses EE-100 through EE-229, 2004-2009. Also included are lists of courses offered and assigned books, circa 2005-2010.
- Faculty files, 1890 -- 2005; 1985 -- 2005; UA240.004; 2.4 Linear Feet
  - William Leslie Hooper engineering notebook, 1890; UA240.004.012; Hooper, William Leslie (Box data_value_missing_7895b037b0187ba7868f5b73396ae225, Box 12)
    Open for research.
  - Joseph P. Noonan, Department Chair, files, 1966 -- 2005; UA240.004.006 (Box 6)
    Documentation of Joseph P. Noonan's work as Professor of Electrical Engineering and Chair of the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering, circa 1985-2005. Records include publications and drafts; papers and theses written by advisees; and correspondence and reports related to the ABET accreditation process for the School of Engineering.
- Eta Kappa Nu files, 1960 -- 2010; UA240.005; 2.4 Linear Feet
  Documentation of the administration and activities of the Tufts University chapter of Eta Kappa Nu, international electrical and computer engineering honor society of the IEEE. Records include rosters of members and officers, programs for initiation banquets, and correspondence with the Eta Kappa Nu national office.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Eta Kappa Nu files, 1960 -- 2010; UA240.005.003 (Box 3)
    Records include rosters of members and officers, programs for initiation banquets, and correspondence with the Eta Kappa Nu national office, circa 1960-2010.
  - Eta Kappa Nu - Epsilon Delta Chapter membership books, 1968-1999; Institutional Research survey results, 1986-1996, UA240.005.011 (Box data_value_missing_a32bb2576a9bdf9d11bf667232d57853, Box 11)
- Photographs, 1935 -- 2005; UA240.006; 3.6 Linear Feet
  Photographs of Electrical and Computer Engineering faculty, students, and events including speaker contests, parties, commencements, and Eta Kappa Nu initiation banquets. Includes albums and loose photographs.
  - Photographs of faculty, students, and events, circa 1935 -- 2005; UA240.006.007 (Box data_value_missing_4f1557faa4318aed2bdf529fb5b490ba, Box 7)
    Photographs of Electrical and Computer Engineering faculty, students, and events including speaker contests, parties, commencements, and Eta Kappa Nu initiation banquets, circa 1915-2005. Most photographs date 1988-2005. Includes albums and loose photographs.
  - Photographs of faculty, students, and events, 1990 -- 2005; UA240.006.008 (Box data_value_missing_4f1557faa4318aed2bdf529fb5b490ba, Box 8)
    Photographs of Electrical and Computer Engineering faculty, students, and events including parties and commencements, circa 1990-2005. Includes albums and loose photographs.
    - Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering students (group photo), 2000 -- 2005; UA240.006.008.00001 (Box Large Map Case 3 Drawer 10)
- 2017 accessions, 2006 -- 2011; UA240.007; 2.4 Linear Feet 2 record cartons
  Materials are arranged in received order.
  Records containing information related to student education, staff and faculty employment, and Board of Trustees records are closed for 75 years from the date of creation.
  This series contains material created or gathered in preparation for and relating to the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering's 2011 accreditation visit from the Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology. It includes course materials, course evaluations, student work, surveys, reports, and notes.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Transferred by the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering, accession UA-2017-043.
  - ABET material: course material and evaluations, reports, student work, 2006 -- 2011; UA240.007.009; 1.2 Linear Feet 1 record carton (Box 9)
    75 years from date of creation.
  - ABET material: course material and evaluations, reports, student work, 2006 -- 2011; UA240.007.010; 1.2 Linear Feet 1 record carton (Box 10)
- 2018 accessions, circa 2004 -- 2018; UA240.008; 6.6 Linear Feet
  This series is arranged in received order.
  This series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
  Transferred by the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering, 2018, accession UA-2019-032.
  This series contains materials required to be collected for two cycles of the Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology (ABET) accreditation process. Materials include semester files, which are folders on each course offered and include course evaluations, quizzes, and student work; course materials binders; and ECE-specific workbooks for certain courses.
  - ABET material: course material and evaluations, reports, student work, 2012 -- 2016; UA240.008.011; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 11)
    This file largely contains course evaluations, and some student work.
  - ABET material: course material and evaluations, reports, student work, 2015 -- 2017; UA240.008.012; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 12)
    In addition to course evaluations and student work, this file contains course binders for EN 01-01 (Hopwood) and EN 01-02 (Vandervelde).
  - ABET material: course material and evaluations, reports, student work, 2015 -- 2017; UA240.008.013; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 13)
    In addition to course evaluations and student work, this file contains course binders for ES 2 (Tracey); ES 3 (Preis); ES 3 (Lasser); ES 4 (Panetta); EE 14 (Chang); and an ABET 2017 Site Visit binder.
  - ABET material: course material and student work, circa 2012 -- 2017; UA240.008.014; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 14)
    This file contains course binders for EE 18 (Vandervelde); EE 21 (Hopwood); EE 22 (Sonkusale); EE 23 (Aeron); EE 24 (Miller); EE 26 (Chang); EE 31 (Lasser); EE 97 (Lasser); and EE 107.
  - ABET material: course material, student work, and ECE workbooks, circa 2012 -- 2018; UA240.008.015; 1.2 Linear Feet (Box 15)
    This file contains course binders for EE 98 (Lasser); Senior Design 2017-2018; EE 103 (Koomson); EE 105 (Khan); EE 107 (Vu); EE 125 (Tracey); EE 126 (Hempstead); EE 127 (Aeron); EE 129 (Chang); and EE 133 (Miller); as well as ECE workbooks for EE 127.
  - ABET material: ECE workbooks, circa 2004 -- 2014; UA240.008.016; .6 Linear Feet (Box 16)
    This file contains ECE workbooks for EE 14, EE 105, EE 106, EE 13, ES 4, ES 3, and EE: Principles and Applications.